<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3D Reconstruction on Resume in English</title>
    <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/tags/3d-reconstruction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3D Reconstruction on Resume in English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/tags/3d-reconstruction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[CVM 2023] Deep Panoramic Depth Prediction and Completion for Indoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Abstract We introduce a novel end-to-end deep learning solution for rapidly estimating a dense spherical depth map of an indoor environment. Our input is a single equirectangular image registered with a sparse depth map, as provided by a variety of common capture setups. Depth is inferred by an efficient and lightweight single-branch network, which employs a dynamic gating system to process together dense visual data and sparse geometric data. We exploit the characteristics of typical man-made environments to efficiently compress multi-resolution features and find short- and long-range relations among scene parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[IEEE TVCG 2022] Instant Automatic Emptying of Panoramic Indoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Nowadays 360° cameras, capable to capture full environments in a single shot, are increasingly being used in a variety of Extended Reality (XR) applications that require specific Diminished Reality (DR) techniques to conceal selected classes of objects. In this work, we present a new data-driven approach that, from an input 360° image of a furnished indoor space automatically returns, with very low latency, an omnidirectional photorealistic view and architecturally plausible depth of the same scene emptied of all clutter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[TOG 2021] Deep3DLayout: 3D reconstruction of an indoor layout from a spherical panoramic image</title>
      <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Recovering the 3D shape of the bounding permanent surfaces of a room from a single image is a key component of indoor reconstruction pipelines. In this article, we introduce a novel deep learning technique capable to produce, at interactive rates, a tessellated bounding 3D surface from a single 360° image. Differently from prior solutions, we fully address the problem in 3D, significantly expanding the reconstruction space of prior solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[CVPR 2021] SliceNet: Deep Dense Depth Estimation From a Single Indoor Panorama Using a Slice-Based Representation</title>
      <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Abstract We introduce a novel deep neural network to estimate a depth map from a single monocular indoor panorama. The network directly works on the equirectangular projection, exploiting the properties of indoor 360 images. Starting from the fact that gravity plays an important role in the design and construction of man-made indoor scenes, we propose a compact representation of the scene into vertical slices of the sphere, and we exploit long- and short-term relationships among slices to recover the equirectangular depth map.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
