<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eva Almansa on Resume in English</title>
    <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eva Almansa on Resume in English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Instant Automatic Emptying of Panoramic Indoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Nowadays 360° cameras, capable to capture full environments in a single shot, are increasingly being used in a variety of Extended Reality (XR) applications that require specific Diminished Reality (DR) techniques to conceal selected classes of objects. In this work, we present a new data-driven approach that, from an input 360° image of a furnished indoor space automatically returns, with very low latency, an omnidirectional photorealistic view and architecturally plausible depth of the same scene emptied of all clutter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep3DLayout: 3D reconstruction of an indoor layout from a spherical panoramic image</title>
      <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Recovering the 3D shape of the bounding permanent surfaces of a room from a single image is a key component of indoor reconstruction pipelines. In this article, we introduce a novel deep learning technique capable to produce, at interactive rates, a tessellated bounding 3D surface from a single 360° image. Differently from prior solutions, we fully address the problem in 3D, significantly expanding the reconstruction space of prior solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SliceNet: Deep Dense Depth Estimation From a Single Indoor Panorama Using a Slice-Based Representation</title>
      <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Abstract We introduce a novel deep neural network to estimate a depth map from a single monocular indoor panorama. The network directly works on the equirectangular projection, exploiting the properties of indoor 360 images. Starting from the fact that gravity plays an important role in the design and construction of man-made indoor scenes, we propose a compact representation of the scene into vertical slices of the sphere, and we exploit long- and short-term relationships among slices to recover the equirectangular depth map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Eva Almansa I am a Marie Skłodowska-Curie Early Stage Researcher in the Visual Computing (ViC) group at the Center for Advanced Studies, Research, and Development in Sardinia (CRS4). I hold a Bachelor Degree in Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence (2015) and a Master Degree of Data Science (2017) from the University of Granada, Spain. I am awarded a fellowship (2020-2023) from the EVOCATION innovative training network under H2020.
Eva Almansa | Semantic Scholar My work’s summary at CRS4 Visual Computing Supervisors: Enrico Gobbetti and Giovanni Pintore (CRS4) Techniques: Deep Learning applied from a single panoramic image to estimate depth maps, estimate 3D mesh model of the boundary surfaces of the architectural layout, RGB-D empty room estimation, and sparse to dense depth estimation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to ask me anything about my work. I am delighted to expand my network of contacts.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network</title>
      <link>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evaalmansa.github.io/EvaAlmansa_Portfolio/partners/</guid>
      <description>I reserve this space for all those people whom I would like to promote, whom I admire for their magnificent vocation.
Marta Almansa (Excellent) Digital Artist Speaks: Spanish / English / German Portfolio &amp;amp; Contact: https://drawingprozac.carrd.co/ </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
